bluesprig.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy Policy | BlueSprig

**We may collect the following types of information:**  
Information we may request includes your name, e-mail address, home address and telephone number. Additional information may be asked when you create an account to purchase our products or services, such as your credit card number and billing information.  
We may collect information about your visits to our websites, including the pages you view, the links you click, search terms you enter and other actions you take in connection with the BlueSprig websites and services. We may also collect certain information from the browser you used to come to our website, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times, the URL of the website that referred you to our website and to which URL you browse away from our site if you click on a link on our site.

**Information collected is used by BlueSprig only in line with the purpose below:**  
Provide, maintain, protect, and improve our products, services, technologies, and communications; Deliver the services and support, or carry out the transactions you have requested; Keep you updated about order status, products info and services available from BlueSprig and its corporate affiliates, promotional offers, newsletters, and surveys; Prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities.  
Personal information collected on BlueSprig sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which BlueSprig or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using a BlueSprig site or service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. BlueSprig abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

**Information sharing**  
BlueSprig only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of BlueSprig with your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. In the event that we contract with a third party to provide some part of the information or service that you have requested, BlueSprig may provide your information to such third party, or such third party may collect information from you on our behalf. By written agreement, these third parties are required to implement similar security measures and to process your information only as authorized by BlueSprig in accordance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

**Information security**  
BlueSprig is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. These measures include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and appropriate encryption and physical security measures.  
While we strive to protect your personal information, BlueSprig cannot ensure or warrant that the personal information or private communications you transmit to us will always remain private, and you do so at your own risk. And it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential when a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information.

**Children**  
This Website is not aimed at children and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. Minors should not use this Website unless supervised by an adult. 

**Other websites**  
BlueSprig websites contain links to other websites. BlueSprig is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites. Users should be aware of this when they leave our sites and review the privacy statements of each website they visit that collects information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by BlueSprig websites.

**Enforcement**  
BlueSprig regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is BlueSprig's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between BlueSprig and an individual.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy.**  
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).
